
export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: `You should increase the distance between your vehicle and the vehicle ahead when you:`,
        options: [`Are following a small passenger vehicle.`, `Are being tailgated by another driver.`, `Are driving more slowly than the posted speed limit.`],
        answer: `Are being tailgated by another driver.`
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: `In which of the following scenarios should your wheels not be pointed straight ahead?`,
        options: [`When waiting to make a left turn at a traffic light.`, `When parked on a hill or sloping driveway.`, `When parked on the side of a level roadway where there is no curb.`],
        answer: `When parked on a hill or sloping driveway.`
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: `If a truck or bus is making a right turn where you also need to make a right turn, you should:`,
        options: [`Quickly turn before the truck or bus is able to.`, `Wait until the truck or bus turns before you turn.`, `Squeeze between the truck or bus and the curb.`],
        answer: `Wait until the truck or bus turns before you turn.`
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: `
        When being followed by a tailgater, which of the following will help you avoid being hit from behind?`,
        options: [`Merging into another lane`, `Decreasing your following distance`, `Changing lanes frequently`],
        answer: `Decreasing your following distance`
    },
    // {
    //     id: 4,
    //     question: `When you see this sign, you:`,
    //     options: [`Are approaching a railroad crossing and should prepare to stop.`, `Will always stop at the upcoming railroad crossing.`, `Should stop and wait for a signal before crossing the railroad tracks.`],
    //     answer: `Are approaching a railroad crossing and should prepare to stop.`
    // },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: `When driving under snowy or icy conditions:`,
        options: [`It is safe to use your cruise control.`, `Make speed and directional changes more gradually than you would otherwise.`, `Drive as you would under normal conditions.`],
        answer: `Make speed and directional changes more gradually than you would otherwise.`
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: `A broken yellow centerline means that:`,
        options: [`Passing is not permitted.`, `Passing on the right is permitted when the way ahead is clear.`, `Passing on the left is permitted when the way ahead is clear.`],
        answer: `Passing on the left is permitted when the way ahead is clear.`
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: `When driving in fog, rain, or snow, use:`,
        options: [`Low beams.`, `High beams.`, `Fog lights only.`],
        answer: `Low beams.`
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: `
        Which of these statements is true about changing lanes?`,
        options: [`You only need to turn and look over your right shoulder for lane changes to the right or left.`, `Look over your right shoulder for a right lane change and your left shoulder for a left lane change.`, `Vehicles with two outside mirrors do not have blind spots.`],
        answer: `Look over your right shoulder for a right lane change and your left shoulder for a left lane change.`
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: `It is illegal for a person 21 years of age or older to drive with a blood alcohol concentration (BAC) that is ___ or higher...`,
        options: [`.08%`, `.10%`, `.05%`],
        answer: `.08%`
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: `You must notify the DMV within 5 days if..`,
        options: [`Sell or transfer your vehicle`, `Are cited for traffic violation`, `Paint your vehicle a different color`],
        answer: `Sell or transfer your vehicle`
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: `At dawn or dusk, or in rain or snow, it can be hard to see and be seen. A good way to let other drivers know you are there is to turn...`,
        options: [`Up the instrument panel lights`, `On your parking lights`, `On your headlights`],
        answer: `On your headlights`
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: `When changing lanes on a freeway, you should..`,
        options: [`Signal for at least 5 seconds`, `Slow down before you start to change lanes`, `Assume there is enough space for your vehicle, if you signal first`],
        answer: `Assume there is enough space for your vehicle, if you signal first`
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: `You are driving in a city street and see an emergency vehicle with flashing lights behind you. What do you do?`,
        options: [`Drive to the right edge of the road and slow down`, `Drive to the right edge of the road and stop`, `Stay in you lane, slow down, and let it pass`],
        answer: `Drive to the right edge of the road and stop`
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: `Large trucks turning right onto a street with two lanes in each direction...`,
        options: [`May complete their turn in either the left or right lane`, `Often have to use part of the left lane to complete the turn`, `Must stay in the right lane at all times`],
        answer: `Often have to use part of the left lane to complete the turn`
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: `You are driving on a one-way street. You may turn left onto another one-way street:`,
        options: [`Only if a sign permits the turn`, `If traffic on the street is moving to the left`, `If traffic on the street is moving to the right`],
        answer: `If traffic on the street is moving to the left`
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: `You want to pass a bicyclist riding on the edge of your lane, You:`,
        options: [`Must Honk your horn before passing the bicyclist`, `Must not squeeze past the bicyclist`, `Must not pass the bicyclist for any reason`],
        answer: `Must not squeeze past the bicyclist`
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: `You should not start across an intersection if you know you will block the intersection when the light turns red:`,
        options: [`Under any circumstances`, `Unless you entered the intersection on a yellow light`, `Unless you entered the intersection on a green light`],
        answer: `Under any circumstances`
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: `When making a right turn, look right and left, yield right-of-way, and turn the steering wheel using:`,
        options: [`Hand off hand technique`, `A double hand technique`, `Single hand technique`, `Hand over hand technique`],
        answer: `Hand over hand technique`
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: `If you approach an intersection at which the traffic lights are not working, you must first _______ for entering the intersection and yield the right of way.`,
        options: [`Turn on emergency lights`, `Reduce your speed`, `Come to a complete stop`, `Increase your speed`],
        answer: `Come to a complete stop`
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: `Must not pass another vehicle if you see:`,
        options: [`An approaching hill or curve where there is no clear visibility`, `Schoolbus ahead with red flashing lights and an extended`, `A solid yellow line in your lane`, `Any of the above situations`],
        answer: `Any of the above situations`
    },
]